[
	{ "question": "blue", "answer": "あおい" },
	{ "question": "apartment house", "answer": "アパート" },
	{ "question": "sweet", "answer": "あまい" },
	{ "question": "(not)very", "answer": "あまり" },
	{ "question": "prefer", "answer": "いい" },
	{ "question": "how many", "answer": "いくつ" },
	{ "question": "how much", "answer": "いくら" },
	{ "question": "welcome!", "answer": "いっらしゃいませ" },
	{ "question": "cow", "answer": "うし" },
	{ "question": "horse", "answer": "うま" },
	{ "question": "yes", "answer": "ええ" },
	{ "question": "fried shrimp", "answer": "エビフライ" },
	{ "question": "yen", "answer": "えん" },
	{ "question": "money", "answer": "おかね" },
	{ "question": "one hundren million", "answer": "おく" },
	{ "question": "plate", "answer": "おさら" },
	{ "question": "boy", "answer": "おとこのこ" },
	{ "question": "noon", "answer": "おひる" },
	{ "question": "girl", "answer": "おんなのこ" },
	{ "question": "very good, sir/certainly, sir", "answer": "かしこまりました" },
	{ "question": "hard", "answer": "かたい" },
	{ "question": "paper", "answer": "かみ" },
	{ "question": "hot(taste)", "answer": "からい" },
	{ "question": "curry", "answer": "カレー" },
	{ "question": "stamp", "answer": "きって" },
	{ "question": "milk", "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう" },
	{ "question": "dislike", "answer": "きらい" },
	{ "question": "please give me~", "answer": "ください" },
	{ "question": "socks", "answer": "くつした" },
	{ "question": "gram", "answer": "グラム" },
	{ "question": "child", "answer": "こ" },
	{ "question": "coffee", "answer": "コーヒー" },
	{ "question": "cola", "answer": "コーラ" },
	{ "question": "glass", "answer": "コープ" },
	{ "question": "classifier for books", "answer": "さつ" },
	{ "question": "juice", "answer": "ジュース" },
	{ "question": "owner", "answer": "しゅじん" },
	{ "question": "kind", "answer": "しんせつ" },
	{ "question": "supermarket", "answer": "スーパー" },
	{ "question": "like", "answer": "すき" },
	{ "question": "stereo", "answer": "ステレオ" },
	{ "question": "thousand", "answer": "せん" },
	{ "question": "yes, it is", "answer": "そうですね" },
	{ "question": "pair of(shoes)", "answer": "そく" },
	{ "question": "classifier for machine and vehicles", "answer": "だい" },
	{ "question": "egg", "answer": "たまご" },
	{ "question": "chest", "answer": "たんす" },
	{ "question": "neighborhood", "answer": "ちかく" },
	{ "question": "classifier for counting large animals", "answer": "とう" },
	{ "question": "how about~", "answer": "どう" },
	{ "question": "please", "answer": "どうぞ" },
	{ "question": "meat", "answer": "にく" },
	{ "question": "classifier for counting people", "answer": "にん" },
	{ "question": "price", "answer": "ねだん" },
	{ "question": "cup of/glass of/bowl of", "answer": "はい" },
	{ "question": "postcard", "answer": "はがき" },
	{ "question": "handkerchief", "answer": "ハンカチ" },
	{ "question": "hamburg steak", "answer": "ハンバーグ" },
	{ "question": "beer", "answer": "ビール" },
	{ "question": "classifier for small animals", "answer": "ひき" },
	{ "question": "hundred", "answer": "ひゃく" },
	{ "question": "convenient", "answer": "べんり" },
	{ "question": "classifier for counting long things", "answer": "ほん" },
	{ "question": "classifier for counting thin/flat things", "answer": "まい" },
	{ "question": "ten thousand", "answer": "まん" },
	{ "question": "mandarin orange", "answer": "みかん" },
	{ "question": "water", "answer": "みず" },
	{ "question": "store/shop", "answer": "みせ" },
	{ "question": "soon", "answer": "もうすぐ" },
	{ "question": "thing/object", "answer": "もの" },
	{ "question": "cooking/dish", "answer": "りょうり" },
	{ "question": "refrigerator", "answer": "れいぞうこ" },
	{ "question": "restaurant", "answer": "レストラン" },
	{ "question": "soft", "answer": "やわらかい" }
]
